(A new era begins in the commerce market.)
(A 500,000-dollar grand prize)
(The biggest
commerce survival competition ever)
(8 teams from 9 countries)
(A fierce sales battle
where national pride is at stake)
This is a commerce war.
Naturally, sales prove your personality.
But the numbers don't lie.
So we're going to find out
when the numbers come in who did the best.
(Using every means necessary)
(Drive the highest sales possible.)
(The war of 40 sellers begins.)
Survival shows are all about momentum.
I must do well no matter what,
and our team must be acknowledged
as a strong one.
Am I scared of the other teams?
Not really.
No. Remember I said that
we should start yesterday?
We can totally catch up.
Oh, no.
(This is wild.)
(Unexpected twists that turn the tables)
(The beginning of unpredictable
and thrilling twists)
We also want to win,
so we will try our best.
(Sales define ability.)
(Sales become a nation's pride.)
X The League, the true sales war,
with each nation’s pride on the line,
begins now.
(It begins now.)
(Korea)
(A selling war
that transcends borders and languages)
(Elite sellers from 9 countries
arrive in Korea.)
(A selling survival competition
on the global stage)
A national commerce showdown...
that will reshape the global market,
X The League.
(Only one nation can rise
to the top of the world.)
(But who will be the one to sit upon
the ultimate throne?)
(The challengers aiming for the crown)
Here are the nation's top sellers.
Korea.
(With the e-commerce market
exceeding 200 billion dollars)
(Speed is a given.
Efficiency is the weapon.)
(The first nation is Korea.)
(The pride of K-commerce is the first
to enter the battlefield.)
(Team Korea)
Noh Hee Young.
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
(Noh Hee Young, Korea's top brand director
for Olive Young, Bibigo, and more)
(The unrivaled Midas
in the lifestyle industry)
Ki Eun Se.
(Ki Eun Se of the live commerce
"Eun Se's Finds")
(Just 10 minutes to sell out)
(Generated 1.1 million dollars in sales
for a fashion brand)
(Sangeun unnie, kkang.stylist, KKAKK UNNI)
The Korean flag gives you that energy.
This is a national competition, after all.
The weight and responsibility
that Team Korea carries.
That's what will drive us
to give it our all.
I believe everyone will do their best.
It was an overwhelming moment.
With an entire nation on the line,
we felt the same sense of duty
as a national team.
(1st generation influencer and actress,
Ki Eun Se)
Vietnam.
(A beauty trendsetter of 17 years,
Sangeun unnie)
(The heart of Southeast Asia's growth)
(A land of opportunity rising again)
(Team Vietnam)
(Welcome.)
(A beauty trendsetter of 17 years,
Sangeun unnie)
Singapore and Malaysia.
Welcome.
(Team SGMY)
(The center of capital and logistics)
(An e-commerce hub
connecting Southeast Asia)
They must be from Malaysia,
and the others from Singapore.
(X The League's only alliance team)
Jianhao Tan.
(A top creator with over
4 billion cumulative views worldwide)
(Singapore's No. 2
social media influencer)
Sonia.
(Malaysian K-beauty sales queen, Sonia)
(Malaysia's K-beauty expert, Sonia)
(A K-beauty trendsetter generating
3.8 million dollars in annual sales)
Japan.
- Japan?
- Japan.
(A blue ocean with the greatest potential
for explosive growth)
(Team Japan)
Ryota.
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
SANA.
(A multi-player generating
1 million dollars in monthly sales)
(A 1st-generation influencer
in social media and entertainment)
Kii chan.
(A viral sensation
featured on OTT's dating show)
(The face behind the gyaru trend
captivating Gen Z worldwide)
The US.
The US!
(A multi-trillion-dollar market
absorbing global consumption)
(Team US)
How gorgeous.
Anyone can tell they're from the US.
Francesca Farago.
(The woman who captivated the world,
Francesca)
(A top influencer
transforming brand value)
Ayanna Sabrina.
(America's Gen Z icon,
a K-beauty commerce star...)
(generating 7.3 million dollars in sales)
Indonesia.
(The largest market
leading Southeast Asia)
(A mega market
with a population of 270 million)
(Team Indonesia)
(Vietnam's Gen Z seller, Khanh Huyen)
Ashanty Hermansyah.
(Family with 100 million followers,
Ashanty)
(A mega influencer
with a total of 100 million followers)
(Indonesian royal family)
Ibnu Wardani.
(Owner of a Diamond Button
with 50 million subscribers)
(Indonesia's No. 1
IT-category mega seller)
Thailand.
(Where tourism meets e-commerce,
the hottest consumer market right now)
So pretty.
(Team Thailand)
(TikTok Shop Top 3 sellout seller,
Yok Thong)
(The beauty commerce queen
chosen by global cosmetics brands)
(Top 3 TikTok Shop seller in Thailand)
Do you know anyone?
I've seen him before.
(Currently active in Thailand)
When Team Thailand appeared,
Fluke was one of the members.
I thought,
"Gosh, he also joined this show?"
(They've become rivals competing under
their nations' names.)
How come they only have four people?
I don't know.
(5 sellers from each nation
have joined X The League.)
Why do they only have four people?
I know, right? Where's the last seller?
Are they not here yet?
(Unlike the other teams,
Team Thailand only has 4 sellers.)
China.
(The last nation)
(Trillions in capital power)
(An unmatched-scale e-commerce empire)
(Team China)
Kwak Cheong.
(The leader driving K-beauty brands
into China)
Ma Lingdao.
(The mastermind behind
50 million dollars in sales, Ma Lingdao)
(Head of creator management
and content strategy)
(A short-form content expert with
50 million dollars in cumulative sales)
To think China would participate.
I know.
I think the most powerful country
is probably China,
just because of sheer numbers.
I believe...
the strongest country is the US.
(Two global powers named each other
as their greatest rivals.)
Wouldn't China or the US,
with the largest pool of consumers,
have an advantage?
(All eyes are on these two global powers,
the US and China)
Honestly,
I felt Indonesia had the biggest chance.
Because when they arrived...
We actually arrived at the airport
with them.
I saw such a big team.
They were all wearing team uniforms,
and they were live-streaming
the moment they arrived.
So it was a little bit intimidating,
I guess.
But yes.
There's not a single
absolutely weak country.
Indonesia has the potential...
to outgun the other teams.
(With a population of 270 million)
(An emerging powerhouse
backed by a massive market)
(Now, Team Indonesia is ready
to take on the world.)
(Top 10 of a seller survival show,
Aom Chr)
(400,000 in sales in 6 minutes, Elle Onni)
What?
It's Tiffany Young.
How pretty.
(The cheerful selling master)
It's BamBam!
(MC Tiffany Young and BamBam)
Oh, my gosh.
(This clip was created
using AI-generated content.)
(A Vietnamese TikToker
with 8.8 million followers, Zahan)
Gosh, I just got goosebumps.
Amazing.
Where are they appearing from?
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
(From where?)
(The MCs make a surprise entrance
from the center.)
(The two MCs
who will lead the long journey)
(1st-generation influencer and actress,
Ki Eun Se)
(Thai idol and actor-turned CEO, Fluke)
This is incredible.
(The cheerful selling master)
Oh, my gosh.
Amazing.
The national commerce showdown
that will reshape the global market,
and each nation's top sellers
who are here...
for X The League's opening ceremony.
Welcome.
I'm Tiffany Young, MC of X The League.
Nice to meet you.
(Top 10 of a seller survival show,
Aom Chr)
I'm BamBam. Nice to meet you.
(MC BamBam)
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
(Singapore's trendsetting influencer,
Debbie Soon)
The nation's top sellers
from the eight nations...
will go through five rounds
in X The League...
and take part in fierce selling wars.
The nation with
the highest cumulative score...
across five rounds
will be crowned the champion.
(5-round total score determines
the champion nation.)
The nation to come in first place...
will receive 500,000 dollars as a prize.
(The final winning nation
wins 500,000 dollars.)
What?
(0-percent return rate based on trust,
Cui Shishi)
(Indonesian superstar, Aurel)
Not only that, the winning nation...
will also receive a benefit...
sellers around the world wish for.
Two million dollars.
(Given 2 million dollars
as a special benefit)
(500,000 dollars in prize,
2 million dollars in special benefit)
Oh, my gosh. I was like,
"Are you kidding me?"
Five hundred thousand?
When I heard it was in US dollars,
I was like, "What?"
I thought, "The prize is no joke."
Now that I know
there's a prize and a benefit,
we'll try hard to come in first place.
I want both the prize and benefit.
(Viral creator with an alter ego)
Everyone, please look up.
(1st-generation influencer and actress,
Ki Eun Se)
(The CEO Hollywood is watching, Stormi)
(Vietnam's Gen Z seller, Khanh Huyen)
You will be able to see the pyramid
that symbolizes X The League.
X The League has tiers.
After each round,
you will be classified into
three different tiers.
The nation's X Tier...
is directly connected to
each round's sales...
and the selling commission.
(Sellers earn commissions
based on sales tiers.)
The Platinum Tier is
ten percent of the sales.
The Emerald Tier is
15 percent of the sales.
The Diamond Tier is
20 percent of the sales.
(Tier-based commission settlement
on sales amounts)
X3 earns twice as much commission as X1.
- That's double the amount.
- Exactly.
(Director of an e-commerce company with
cumulative sales of 100 million dollars)
It was 10 percent, 15 percent,
and 20 percent.
Although the number sounds like it's only
a five-percent difference from another,
when it comes to commission,
the percentage,
the five percent
makes a lot of difference.
Five percent is unreal.
And I really hope we win...
because that would be
an amazing advantage for our team.
We must come in the top two
no matter what.
I thought about...
how we could make that happen,
either in 1st or 2nd place.
I wanted us to earn the biggest commission
in Round One. The Platinum Tier.
That was all I could think about.
We're on this show to win.
Let's compete! Let's fight!
(The sellers' first thrilling showdown
begins soon.)
(Who will deliver the pitch
that captures customers?)
(The ultimate selling battle, coming soon)
Moving on, we will introduce
the sellers of X The League.
Team China. Let's meet Team China.
The team facing pressure
from every nation.
China, with its overwhelming scale.
Kwak Cheong, the owner leading Team China.
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Kwak Cheong, the owner of Team China.
Her Korean is good.
Incubating doesn't mean raising children.
My role is to help brands grow...
by analyzing products,
studying data, and providing insights...
from various perspectives
to ensure their long-term success...
in the Chinese market.
I started live commerce ten years ago.
Now, I even operate
a live commerce company.
I've been working hard around the clock
to keep it growing.
I took one step at a time,
starting from sales of zero yuan...
and then achieving...
sales of tens of millions of Chinese yuan.
(Kwak Cheong will lead Team China
with her years of experience.)
X The League will be a chance...
to tell the world that...
the future of live commerce
will be that of...
China's current live commerce,
which will be great.
Your Korean is amazing.
I thought I was listening to a translator.
Me too.
All right, moving on,
Ma Lingdao of Team China.
My keyword is black hole.
What's the meaning of black hole?
In China, it's known as "heidong."
Live commerce is essentially built
on two things,
short-form content...
and live streaming.
(Driving sales through links
embedded in content)
(Boosting real-time sales
through live commerce)
What's most important
during live commerce is,
whether the customer watches your video
or live show,
to captivate them with the content.
Like getting sucked into a black hole,
it's making the customers
unable to get out of the content.
I've been to China on a study tour.
One of the members was a black hole.
They were outstanding.
China's e-commerce and live shopping...
are much ahead of ours.
- It's now time to meet the next team.
- Okay.
Here's Team US.
One member stands out in Team US.
Ayanna Sabrina's keyword is...
Gen Z trendsetter.
Gen Z Icon.
She looks familiar.
I've seen her before.
Gen Z Icon. That's cool.
(38-hour non-stop live)
Gen Z Icon.
I received the same award as her...
in China two years ago.
The award was given
to the biggest influencers...
in each nation.
When I saw her back then,
her sales were amazing.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Ayanna Sabrina.
I'm a 25-year-old social commerce seller.
And in the space,
I gained over two million followers.
In the past two years,
I generated over seven million dollars,
especially in the K-beauty space.
I feel like in the space,
I have to represent...
the girls who look like me.
Who want to try K-beauty
and don't know where to start,
and that's where I come in.
(Ayanna works as a K-beauty creator.)
And even though I'm young,
I'm still confident,
I'm sales-driven,
and I turn influence into impact.
- As expected from Team US.
- She's cool.
She's suddenly making me nervous as well.
Moving on,
the owner of Team Korea, Noh Hee Young.
I heard you recruited
Korea's top sellers yourself.
I'm Noh Hee Young,
the woman who makes brands.
Hi.
I actually haven't counted...
how many brands I've launched
or rebranded.
But the news articles say
I've worked on around 200 brands,
and I've opened...
around 2,500 offline stores.
I actually think people can succeed...
when they have a complex.
I was a businessperson until I was 43.
(Noh Hee Young ran a restaurant
in Apgujeong.)
"Noh Hee Young can only target
small areas..."
"like Apgujeong-dong and Cheongdam-dong."
"She won't be able to make a brand
beloved by the whole nation."
When I heard people say that,
I thought,
"No, I'll make the best brand in Korea."
I had the resolution.
So I joined Orion past the age of 40.
I wanted to make a nationwide brand
like Choco Pie,
thus I came up with Market O Brownie.
Next, I joined CJ...
and transformed Olive Young to a place
where you could test the products.
CGV became a place
where you want to visit.
Bibigo, and many more.
(The undisputed brand maker in Korea,
Noh Hee Young)
I've made many successful brands,
so I want to make Team Korea
of X The League...
a successful brand as well.
Gosh, that's a lot of brands.
She's very skilled.
Amazing.
I got various products...
which we could sell best...
from each category.
I can confidently introduce them
as the most powerful team.
Aren't you looking forward to Team Korea?
- Yes, I am.
- Right.
Let's meet the captain of Team Indonesia.
Ashanty Hermansyah.
Her keyword is "100-million star."
One hundred million?
That's impressive.
She's on another level.
One-hundred-million star.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I'm Ashanty,
the captain of Team Indonesia.
I have a husband, 4 children,
and 2 grandchildren.
The number of followers of my family
adds up to 100 million.
I've worked as a content creator
for the past 8 to 9 years,
and my whole family works
as content creators.
(A famous celebrity and a mega seller
in Indonesia)
With the support of the people
of Indonesia, we can succeed.
(Captain Ashanty incurs high sales
from her strong fan base.)
My oldest child that came with me...
has 35.79 million followers.
The whole family is "mega."
They're a family of influencers.
They're like the Kardashians.
It looks like it.
I really didn't think
they were mother and daughter.
They're basically fans of the family.
If it's 100 million followers in total,
that's more than the population of Korea.
(1st-generation influencer and actress,
Ki Eun Se)
Let's meet the next seller.
Mami Louisse.
Her keyword is "38 hours."
Thirty-eight hours.
Hello.
- Hello.
Hello, everyone.
So, my name is Mami Louisse.
Why 38 hours?
Because I turn on my live streamings...
for very long.
I do live streaming for 38 hours nonstop.
For 38 hours?
Thirty-eight hours of live streaming.
Without sleeping?
What?
For 38 hours?
How? I think everybody is curious.
How do you...
Yes, how do you do that?
Thirty-eight hours live streaming,
nonstop.
I can do it.
For 38 hours?
Yes.
Actually, I've already been doing
live streaming for almost four years.
I always live stream nonstop every day.
(Malaysian K-beauty sales queen)
Thirty-eight hours
from the Indonesian team.
That one was crazy for me.
Because I have been doing live streaming.
The maximum would be 4 or 5 hours.
That would be the maximum for me.
- Thirty-eight hours...
- Exactly.
was her keyword.
The keyword got everyone on their toes.
The next team on X The League.
They're the only allied team.
The alliance of two countries.
Singapore and Malaysia.
Sonia.
Your keyword is "K-wifey."
K-wifey?
- K-wifey?
She must be Korean.
Thank you.
Hello.
I can speak a bit of Korean.
She's not.
Yes.
Hello, everyone. I'm Sonia.
I'm from Malaysia.
I'm a Malaysian Chinese.
The reason
why people call me K-wifey is...
because I actually dated
a Korean boyfriend.
But also, one of the reasons
I'm here today is because...
I really love discovering
K-beauty products.
I always bring a lot of K-beauties...
and K-fashion to Malaysia,
and because Malaysians love
Korean culture as well.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me too.
Kathy Phol of Team Thailand.
Kathy Flow.
Hello. I'm basically Kathy Phol.
I was an influencer
in luxurious lifestyle,
but I wanted to change,
so I turned into a live seller.
(Kathy became famous
for her luxurious lifestyle contents.)
My family wants for nothing,
but I've had the thirst
for accomplishing something on my own.
So I started a live commerce
on my social media.
But live streaming can't be perfect...
every single time.
I rather prefer that
because it's more challenging that way.
It stimulates me.
I started the live commerce business...
last November.
It's been about 4 to 5 months now.
I have my nickname as a seller.
Kathy Flow.
Cash flow.
Ta-da.
I'm here to shake this whole thing up.
And our team is going to win.
Let's go.
- Straight to the point.
- Yes.
(Thai silver spoon seller, Kathy)
As you can see,
one seat is empty.
Exactly.
One seat is empty.
As the Thai representative, I...
Can I say this?
- Of course you can.
- Can I?
When you talk about Thailand,
you think of BamBam.
Thank you. So...
to let the whole world know
about my country's sellers,
I've become the owner.
Is that why you said that?
(The pioneer of K-beauty in China,
Kwak Cheong)
(No. 1 tech sales in Indonesia, Ibnu)
BamBam.
I can't believe this.
Plot twist.
Hello.
(The owner of Team Thailand
is none other than BamBam.)
Isn't that team too strong?
That's dangerous.
Like a dad,
since they've come all the way to Korea,
I'll take care of and look after them.
I'll lead you all like a mom.
I could connect them to the brands...
and help them with the future sales.
That's what I'm hoping for.
I'll carry on those roles as the owner.
Thank you.
If BamBam appears on my live stream,
all the products will be sold out.
I knew Thailand was one of the teams
we had to watch out for.
And now we know.
With that, I've introduced the sellers
of X The League.
Languages, backgrounds, and careers...
may all be different,
but they've all made big impacts
on the global market.
I can't wait to find out
how they'll compete against each other...
for the actual competition.
(Annual revenue of 20 million dollars,
fashion influencer)
I don't think...
Japan often does live commerce,
so they might be rather weak at it.
As for Vietnam...
I thought we'd have a chance
against Team Vietnam.
I think my team is the best.
The other teams... yes.
Am I scared of the other teams?
Not really.
Yes, the Gen Z icon.
She said she's met me before?
(TikTok Shop millionaire, Ayanna)
I don't know anyone.
To me, the gross merchandise volume,
or GMV,
is a piece of cake.
(The prelude to war)
The sellers, who have climbed to the top
in different markets,
are now competing on the same platform.
It's your first chance
to explore each other,
which could change the tide
of the competition.
The First Pitch starts now.
(Round 1 pre-mission, The First Pitch)
(It's time to validate the sellers' skills
before the main round starts.)
(TikTok Shop millionaire, Ayanna)
(The pre-mission)
The evaluation has already started.
(1-million-dollar monthly sales, SANA)
For The First Pitch,
each country's sellers...
will pitch a randomly-assigned product...
to show off the country's prowess.
- Random?
(A creator with 10 million fans,
Jianhao Tan)
When the country and their product
is revealed,
- you will have five minutes to prepare...
- Five minutes?
the pitch.
When you are ready,
a timer of 180 seconds
for the pitch will start running.
(Round 1 pre-mission: The products
and pitching order are matched randomly.)
(After a 5 minute of discussion,
all teammates except the owner pitch.)
Once the pitching is over,
you will rank...
the other countries excluding your own,
from 1 to 7.
The country which places first...
will be rewarded with a strong benefit.
(A beauty trendsetter of 17 years,
Sangeun unnie)
Oh, my gosh.
(A creator strategist, Joanne)
(At the mention of the benefit,
the atmosphere shifts.)
After the results are announced,
they can select...
the country of their choice.
(We can select?)
(What's the benefit of the pre-mission?)
They can steal five percent
of the selected country's...
total revenue.
(1st generation influencer and actress)
Five percent? That's a lot.
Five percent.
(It's a golden opportunity
to steal the revenue from another team.)
- Is it a war from the start?
- It's a war.
(The sales war have started
with the pre-mission.)
It was amazing and shocking.
We can acquire part of the revenue...
of our targeted country.
For example, if there's a country
with a large population...
and high revenue,
taking five percent from them
would be huge.
Five percent of the total,
that felt like such a big number.
So we were all excited to learn that...
we could get five percent, which is a lot.
I know how big five percent is.
I'll do my very best
and secure first place.
We must never get selected.
Nice, this benefit makes everything...
all the more interesting.
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman,
Thanh Tuyen)
Everyone must be curious about...
what product you'll be pitching.
(Half-worried)
Please reveal the products now.
(The first mission products
of the top sellers are revealed.)
(Curious)
(No. 1 tech sales in Indonesia, Ibnu)
(10 mission products randomly selected
from various categories)
The key to this mission is...
how you'll pitch the product...
you'll be randomly matched to.
(Which team will secure
the 5-percent steal ticket...)
(with a persuasive pitch?)
Okay, which one's ours?
I think it's all about teamwork.
- Yes.
- Teamwork. Okay.
I was very confident.
I looked forward to it a lot too.
If we get a shirt or a tumbler,
I'm sure we can make a great pitch.
My heart was like, "Oh, my gosh."
I was excited.
I was so excited to do this
because I'm like,
I sell every day. I'm always
pushing out products every day.
So this is my thing. This is my niche.
My heart aches from being nervous.
It aches.
- Oh, here?
- Seriously.
Your heart is on the left side.
(He sure is rational.)
BamBam, please take your seat...
as the team owner.
I believe in Team Thailand.
I'm confident that you'll do well.
We shall start now.
Which country will draw
strong reactions...
and establish dominance over others
with The First Pitch?
Please show us the country
and their product to pitch.
I really did not expect that.
In front of 42 other sellers,
so that was definitely a new experience.
Since I've come all the way here,
I have no choice but to do my best.
I do feel pressured, but I can do it.
I'll enjoy it like a game.
I'll do my best to win first place.
I flew 5 to 6 hours to get here.
I can't go back empty-handed.
Please show us the country
and their product to pitch.
(Which team will pitch first?)
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
(Indonesian superstar, Aurel)
Oh, my gosh, I'm nervous.
I hope we don't go first.
Please no.
- I hope we're not going first.
- I know.
I'm so nervous.
Please.
(Everyone wants to avoid going first.)
(The first team to go is Team Indonesia.)
Indonesia.
- Oh, dear, it's Indonesia.
- Yes.
- Team Indonesia.
- Team Indonesia, let's go.
That was so random. Okay, that's fast.
That was scary.
(Global reality star and top seller,
Francesca)
Thank goodness it's not us.
Team Indonesia, your product is...
a tumbler.
Oh, my gosh. It's a tumbler.
They got a tumbler.
We missed it.
- Tumblers.
(The first mission product, tumblers)
I do think the bottle is the hardest.
A bottle is just a bottle.
But what makes it so special is,
we are here.
(Malaysian K-beauty sales queen)
This is easy to explain.
Everyone uses it.
The average order value isn't high either.
Let's see how good they can sell
water bottles now.
(What is Team Indonesia's strategy?)
I'll explain.
Stainless steel.
Stainless steel, lasts for 30 hours.
I've often sold tumblers in Indonesia.
So when we got tumblers...
(No. 1 tech sales in Indonesia)
This is my specialty.
(Why is he so confident?)
(The owner of the Diamond Play Button)
(No. 1 tech sales in Indonesia, Ibnu)
I have over 50 million followers
across all the platforms.
(A mega seller
who moves 50 million followers)
(Bring it on.)
(5-minute strategy meeting)
Let us speak one by one.
We shouldn't cross talk.
Who wants to go first?
I'll go, and I'll hand it over to Mami.
(Ibnu volunteers
to be the first to pitch.)
I really want to win this.
- You can do this, right?
- Of course I can.
The owner, please go back to your seat.
Team Indonesia, we shall start...
the very first The First Pitch.
- Good luck.
- You can do it.
(Nervous)
Team Indonesia's First Pitch...
starts now.
Does anyone here get angry easily?
Or is anyone stressed?
Anyone? No?
Then take this tumbler!
(TikTok Shop millionaire, Ayanna)
(J-beauty gyaru icon, Kii chan)
(His outburst makes everyone shocked.)
(Global reality star and top seller,
Francesca)
Then take this tumbler!
You can't do this.
(Flustered)
It's bad to throw the product.
It's really bad.
(Thai idol and actor-turned CEO)
If that happens in China,
it's a huge blooper.
(K-influencer with 2.8 million dollar
monthly sales, Xiaoshu Ouni)
It's not a luggage.
You don't really get to throw around
tumblers like that.
(Ibnu displays its durability
in an aggressive way.)
(An unexpected performance)
It could've broken.
That was my idea.
Hundred percent from my brain.
I wanted to show
how sturdy the tumbler was.
I'll throw it.
(Throwing the tumbler was planned.)
When Ibnu throws it,
we should act surprised.
And you continue with your explanation
right away, okay?
(A smooth pitch as they planned)
Stop. Okay, I know.
This is a very good quality.
(Global reality star and top seller,
Francesca)
And the water is kept cold
for as long as 30 hours. Pour in some ice.
(Pour in some ice.)
- It all got dented.
- What?
It all got dented.
(The tumbler is badly dented.)
It's all dented.
It holds 600ml, which is perfect to use.
You can carry it to the gym,
or to go on a stroll.
It's very light.
This tumbler is very good.
Buy it right now.
Thank you, everyone.
- Thank you.
(Glancing around)
(That's it?)
What?
- They have a lot of time left.
- The energy...
(Even after their closing sentence,
they have 99 seconds left.)
They're done in one minute.
You still have some time left!
(Indonesian K-beauty owner, AYU Hur)
Not finished!
More!
Honestly, my mind went blank.
I don't know why.
I finished the explanation in one minute.
Maybe I spoke too fast.
We were left with two minutes.
We have a lot of time left.
There's still more time.
Shall we do more?
I'm sure you'll be satisfied
with this tumbler...
when you use it yourself.
(They belatedly continue with the pitch.)
(But people have
already lost their focus.)
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
(Cold)
(Top 10 of a seller survival show,
Aom Chr)
I think it might be important...
to do the live with all the time we have.
- Yes.
(Team Indonesia became an example
of what other teams shouldn't do.)
The healthy life starts now.
Buy it right now.
Thank you.
(They could not make full use
of all the time given to them.)
The first minute was really good.
We were all impressed.
That's a very bad method.
They have different points.
The thing they emphasized most
was how sturdy the product is.
A tumbler being sturdy
shouldn't be its most outstanding point.
Yes. There are so many things
to talk about. Its design, for one.
The introduction was good.
(A Vietnamese TikToker
with 8.8 million followers, Zahan)
Those who like the thrill
would like that part.
Thank you.
(What result will Team Indonesia get?)
Moving on,
let's see which team and product...
will go second.
(Malaysian K-beauty sales queen, Sonia)
- Please.
- Please, let us go later.
Let us go later.
Please don't be us.
The pressure is real.
(0-percent return rate based on trust)
(The second team is Team Korea.)
- Goodness.
- It's us.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my gosh.
(The pioneer of K-beauty in China,
Kwak Cheong)
(Relieved)
What product will we get?
What product?
(What product will they pitch?)
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
- It's protein shake.
- Protein shake.
(The product for Team Korea
is protein shake.)
I had a feeling we'd get this.
I didn't want to do the shake.
I feel like, I don't know.
All you can do is just drink it.
It's boring.
Good, protein shake is already taken
by someone else.
(They all seem to want
to avoid protein shake.)
(A creator with 10 million fans,
Jianhao Tan)
Team Korea, come to the center...
and discuss your strategy
and set up your product.
Two of you come forward and explain
like a show host.
What's good about it...
and what kind of people should consume it.
Two of you,
mix it with water and drink it.
Like models.
- You get what I mean, right?
- Like this.
Things get complicated when you all try...
to say your own things.
There are so many other shakes out there,
so how is ours different...
from the rest?
And how well it gets dissolved.
She concisely explained...
the selling point of the product.
She felt so reliable
during that short period of time.
(After directing the strategy,
Team Korea's owner returns to her seat.)
I'm looking forward to Team Korea.
Team Korea will do it home shopping style.
It's the official way.
Team Korea's...
First Pitch starts now.
(20 million dollars annual sales
fashion influencer, kkang.stylist)
We'll do well and get the benefit
no matter what.
I'll crush them all.
(Director of an e-commerce company with
cumulative sales of 100 million dollars)
Hello, everyone.
Today, I'd like to introduce
this protein shake to you.
You can tell
from one look at my body, right?
How well I manage my weight.
I've been maintaining this body shape
for ten years.
The secret to maintaining this weight
for ten years is...
keeping my diet low carb and high fat
for a very long time.
One of the keys to maintaining
my low-carb, high-fat diet is...
this protein shake.
Have a look at the nutritional facts.
You must always make sure to choose...
a product which has 20g or more protein.
And this product satisfies
the 20g protein requirement.
Team Korea feels very formal and official.
(Top 10 of a seller survival show,
Aom Chr)
Yes, they make it very formal.
- How does it taste?
- What does it taste like?
I put in a lot of effort
into staying in shape.
I've tried many products,
- but this is very savory and tasty.
- I see. It's tasty.
Just pour in the water, shake it,
and pour it out like this.
Do you see
how all the powder has dissolved?
And it's so thick.
They're really doing it
the home shopping style.
They're very well-organized.
They have a very good system in place.
Yes. They even have the taste testers.
Not only protein,
but it also contains
minerals and vitamins.
- It's very nutritious.
- You can consume enough nutrients...
for one meal with this shake.
I recommend it to those
who want to become pretty or handsome.
Thank you.
(Team Korea ends their pitch neatly.)
(Satisfied)
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
Their teamwork is amazing.
Everybody has their own section.
I think that is
what we're going to improvise.
They're very calm.
They're experts.
(One team keeps a close eye
on Team Korea.)
Every country has different styles
and different ways that work.
The most important thing is,
we want to really show our strength.
My role was
to really focus on the price...
and make people want
to order our product that time.
(What is Team Singapore and Malaysia's
pitch going to be like?)
Good afternoon, everyone.
We're from Singapore and Malaysia.
How many of you guys over here...
love your coffee and your tea?
Well, because these guys drink at least...
Tiffany drinks coffee a lot?
Then you are our potential audience
for now.
Smell my breath.
(Suddenly attacking with his bad breath)
(Quickly evacuating)
- It's not that bad.
- He also has the smell.
I brushed my teeth today,
but I didn't use this.
So this brand is called Euthymol.
And for now, in our live,
only for today...
And the special price for now is...
buy one, and you're going to get...
an actual packaging of another one.
And for this, only for five minutes,
we have limited stock.
They came up with fake pricing.
They're treating this one
as a live commerce.
- Yes.
- They're like, "This is a plus one."
It really looks like
they're live streaming.
We have limited stock,
with adding another one for free.
So it's around one.
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman)
You can clearly see
each country's preferred style.
(Home shopping: A one-way communication,
its goal is to help the viewers...)
(understand and purchase the products...)
(by explaining professionally
and in detail.)
(Explaining, tasting,)
(and demonstrating)
(Team Korea demonstrated
a systematic home shopping style.)
(Live commerce:
A real-time interactive communication)
(It encourages the viewers
to make their purchases...)
(by interacting with the customers
immediately.)
(They approached it in a friendly manner
as if they're interacting real time.)
(Team Singapore and Malaysia pitched in
the form of an interactive live commerce.)
(The two teams have
completely different styles.)
Three seconds left.
You guys have three seconds left.
All right.
(The textbook example of live commerce,
Team Singapore and Malaysia's pitch ends.)
Thank you so much.
The selling styles are so crazy different.
(The CEO Hollywood is watching, Stormi)
So different for everyone.
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
Please show us the next country...
and their product.
(Thai idol and actor-turned CEO, Fluke)
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
I think it's going to be us, guys.
She looked right at us.
(0-percent return rate based on trust,
Cui Shishi)
(They're halfway
through the pre-mission now.)
(K-influencer with 2.8 million dollar
monthly sales, Xiaoshu Ouni)
(Which country will pitch next?)
The 4th team of the 1st Pitch
is Team Vietnam.
(A Vietnamese TikToker
with 8.8 million followers, Zahan)
(Finally.)
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman,
Thanh Tuyen)
The product is collagen.
This is difficult.
(Collagen is difficult to pitch.)
In Vietnam, their live commerce market
is so well-developed.
So they'll do well.
Vietnam is so much younger than Korea
in terms of the e-commerce trend.
This isn't an easy fight, to be honest.
(Vietnam is a formidable opponent
in e-commerce.)
Collagen, let's go.
Team Vietnam's First Pitch starts now.
Go back to your seats now.
(The teammates go back to their seats?)
Where is everyone going?
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
The owner's staying there?
Why isn't the owner returning to her seat?
(The owners must return to their seats
according to the rule.)
The team owner's going to do it?
Oh, my gosh.
What's happening?
(A creator with 10 million fans,
Jianhao Tan)
(While the teammates return to
their seats, the 180-second timer began.)
As you all know, the team owner...
must not be involved
with the first pitch presentation.
You might think this is a simple mission,
but my idea was different.
"Welcome to exclusive live streaming."
Let's try that.
It's more fun to take turns to explain.
And it'll draw more attention.
(The teammates come up
with the pitching strategy.)
(The owner heard
the teammates' conversation.)
(She suddenly summons her teammates.)
You all saw...
that the host sends the owner in.
But I will...
make the presentation for our team.
(The owner suggests pitching alone.)
I think we should all go up
and help each other.
We can split the roles.
I won't be able to focus
with you on stage.
(The owner insists pitching alone
despite the team's concern.)
I've been sitting here...
watching your presentation...
I can't believe it.
I was like, "Oh, my gosh."
Why is she left alone?
(1-million-dollar monthly sales, SANA)
As I watched other teams' presentations,
it felt like watching
the seller's life exactly as it is.
We must look up the product information,
study the customers' complaints,
and deeply understand who the target is...
in order to increase the sales.
I didn't know the owner was allowed.
I think that's against the rules.
That's not right.
(The participating countries are disturbed
as she breaks the rule.)
I'm sure everyone here
represents their countries.
(The owner hasn't even started
explaining the product yet.)
(A Vietnamese TikToker
with 8.8 million followers, Zahan)
(A famous Vietnamese former idol
seller, Hai Dang Doo)
(There's nothing Team Vietnam can do.)
The answer to my question is this product.
(She begins explaining the product
with 30 seconds remaining.)
She's finally talking about the product.
- She's describing it with story telling.z
- I know.
(A beauty trendsetter of 17 years,
Sangeun unnie)
I get why she intended...
to pitch alone.
But I'm not sure if it was a good idea.
Don't hesitate to choose this product.
Thank you.
(She finished pitching
with 15 seconds remaining.)
(The cheerful selling master, Ryota)
What? Is she done?
(The owner returns after pitching.)
Thank you to Team Vietnam
for their First Pitch.
(Vietnam's popular actor
and food CEO, Viet Anh)
I wonder. Did everybody not want to do it?
She was a bit...
The rule said the team owner
must not participate.
It's not a bad way to sell it,
but I don't think it was effective.
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman,
Thanh Tuyen)
(Her pitching only received criticisms.)
I'd be lying if I said I have no regrets.
I hope she realizes her failure,
so she can learn her lesson.
She needs to learn the importance
of the rule.
And the way she competes with other teams.
(The First Pitch, interim status)
(Remaining products: bubble mask pack,
facial cream, shirt, eye cream,)
(feminine cleanser, shampoo)
Now,
please show us...
(What's the next pitching item?)
the next country and the product.
It's the lift booster.
(The next product is
the bubble mask pack.)
(The lift boosting mask pack is
a rising K-beauty product.)
Beauty. I've been doing skincare.
But it's mostly a lot of K-beauty.
I think my main content is beauty.
(The US is a beauty power.)
Beauty is my major.
I introduce
a lot of Korean cosmetic products...
and skincare products.
(China is another beauty power.)
(Who's going to pitch the beauty product?)
I'm getting anxious as it goes.
I think it's finally our turn.
It's probably going to be us.
The fifth country is Team US.
Air bubble mask.
- Okay.
- Beat it.
We were pretty surprised.
That was my initial choice.
Kind of what I wanted to do,
and we got it.
Okay. We got this.
So we got this.
(Team US walks with confidence.)
Aren't they mostly beauty sellers?
- They said they sell beauty...
- Yes.
(The CEO Hollywood is watching, Stormi)
(A model as well as an actress)
(Beauty content with 2.3 million views,
Stormi)
Francesca looks more like
a beauty creator...
than an influencer.
(Beauty content with 1.19 million views,
Francesca)
(Beauty content with 2.64 million views,
Ayanna)
A beauty item is perfect for them.
I'm like, this is my go-to item.
I already had ideas in my head spinning.
And my biggest thing was storytelling,
you know?
Selling the dream of the product.
Not just the product itself.
(As Team US walks with confidence...)
(Groaning)
(Bitter groaning from here and there)
(K-influencer with 2.8-million-dollar
monthly sales, Xiaoshu Ouni)
What do we have left?
The cream...
(Team China checks
on the remaining products.)
The shirt.
(When the pitching products
were revealed...)
What?
I didn't expect to see clothes.
Because I was expecting
skincare products mostly.
(The only clothes among the 10 products)
I'm sick of it.
That's what I hate the most.
I hate clothing the most.
I opened a clothing store before,
and it went completely under.
To me,
clothing is my weak link.
Everyone in Team China focuses
on the skincare...
or inner beauty products.
(Team China's main product genre is
clear.)
(As other team's pitching product is
determined...)
Is it going to be either clothes or cream?
Take the shirt.
(Team China became worried.)
We might receive clothing.
(Storytelling beauty seller, Ran Gaoming)
Your product is the shirt.
(It became true!)
(Storytelling beauty seller, Ran Gaoming)
We're doomed.
It was shocking.
No way. Did we really get the shirt?
(Team China is given the product
everyone wanted to avoid.)
(K-influencer with 2.8-million-dollar
monthly sales, Xiaoshu Ouni)
(Whereas Team US met the best product.)
Okay. It's okay.
(The two prominent countries known
for e-commerce)
(Who's going to do the First Pitch
from these two countries?)
Team US' First Pitch. Let's begin.
(Who's going to do the First Pitch
in Team US?)
Okay.
Have you ever struggled with dry skin?
Have you ever struggled with lack of time?
Have you ever struggled
with not looking like Team Korea?
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
(1st-generation influencer and actress)
Team US has quick thinking.
The moment they mentioned my team,
it drew attention.
We were thinking
only two sides of the stage.
So we only looked forward.
But Team US looked...
in all directions.
(By going in all directions,
they drew more attention.)
I'm going to be showing you
how I transform from this...
to absolutely beautiful...
and under a minute and 38 seconds.
(Team US begins
the product demonstration.)
(Handful)
Amazing.
Shaving...
(Demonstrating after showing
the unique characteristic of the product)
Watch the hair.
- I got this.
- Watch the hair.
They're doomed.
She applied too much.
(Plenty)
What we knew about the product is that
you put it on,
left it on, and it'd absorb.
We have to do a live demonstration
of putting it on,
and we'll show everybody
how the products actually work.
Who is a mom here?
Who is a parent?
Who struggles with having enough time
to actually...
put your makeup on in the morning
or wash your face...
before you take your kids to school?
I know. I'm a mom too.
The morning rush is so real.
This makes it simple.
One step you're cleansing.
It's also a collagen booster.
It also layers underneath your skincare
and your makeup.
So, I know, as you can see...
And in just a few short minutes,
less than that, you can see...
it's fully absorbed into my skin.
We didn't even have to wipe it off at all.
And now I'm ready to go on about my day.
Put on my fresh coat of makeup.
And have completely moisturized
and beautiful skin underneath.
Thank you, everyone.
(Team US' First Pitch ends.)
(Korea's top brand planner)
They're good. Team US is good.
They know how to draw attention.
I believe we have to
give accurate information...
and at the same time, we have to show...
that it's a good product.
They fulfilled both elements.
(What's Team China's strategy
who wanted to avoid the shirt?)
Let's sell under the assumption
that it comes in diverse colors.
(Thinking)
(Since Team China wasn't confident,)
(they think carefully.)
This is kind of difficult.
I think it's going to be harder...
compared to other countries.
I think I can start.
I don't need to emphasize
on how nice it is.
This is a basic item.
It's like rice.
(Something one must get
even though they already have it)
What we need to show is
usage and simpleness.
We can show them by coming up
with different situations.
(Organizing the direction
of their pitching)
Okay.
I have a feeling they'll do well.
Let's watch.
Look at this shirt I'm holding.
Does it look ordinary?
(Team China starts
by showing the product.)
Imagine you're dining out.
You might order a lot of dishes.
Yet, rice is a must.
Your wardrobe is the same.
Everyone needs a basic shirt
that's simple and goes with anything.
(Emphasizing the need by using a metaphor)
You can style this shirt in many ways.
After work, take off your suit,
and simply put it on.
(Ma Lingdao's after work outfit)
(The correct style)
(The unexpected style livens up the mood.)
Cool.
I'm 197.5cm tall.
I need to get 3XL at least.
(The unexpected shirt style)
It's like a fashion show.
(How did the two countries do?)
Next.
(The remaining countries are...)
(Team Japan...)
(and Team Thailand.)
Show us the next country and the product.
(Nervous)
Isn't it about our turn now?
I think it'll be our turn soon.
The seventh country is Japan.
(The 7th 1st Pitch, Team Japan)
(Just as expected)
It's Japan.
(Thai idol and actor-turned CEO, Fluke)
(What is Team Japan going to introduce?)
The product is...
the shampoo.
(Team Japan is going to pitch
the shampoo.)
- Good luck.
Someone has to wash their hair.
If they really do, that's dogged.
I doubt it.
This is kind of hard.
(Storytelling beauty seller)
- it's hard to sell shampoo.
- Yes.
When they can only explain by talking.
Are they going to wash their hair?
(Not easy to demonstrate the product)
(What's Team Japan's strategy?)
Live commerce isn't very active...
in Japan.
We're probably
the last country to start...
among all the countries
that are participating.
We don't have much experience...
of selling something extensively in Japan.
We didn't exactly compete...
based on our sales performance.
(Magazine model)
(Make over)
(Street variety show)
(Team Japan focuses more
on content than commerce.)
I thought we should compete...
with a Japanese-style strategy.
(What's Team Japan's
Japanese style strategy?)
Team Japan's first pitch. Let's begin.
(Good luck.)
(Team Japan's First Pitch starts.)
My name is Ryota.
(Turning)
Beautiful girl. Oh, my gosh.
(A cute girl catches Ryota's eyes.)
My name is Ryota.
I think it's a show.
That's typical of Japan.
It feels like watching a play.
I performed as a comedian in Japan.
I asked my teammates
if it was okay to put on a comedy show.
They were all happy to do it.
Coffee?
(Team Japan chose to put on a skit.)
- No. Sorry.
- No?
(Ryota was rejected by a girl.)
Oh, my gosh.
- What is that smell?
- Oh, my gosh.
I like the idea. I like the skit.
You can't date a girl if your hair smells.
Come on.
Hi.
- Now, this shampoo...
- Really?
(What's he doing?)
Is he really washing his hair?
I'd pass out if he really washes his hair.
(He's washing his hair...)
(He's washing his hair in the studio.)
You get so many bubbles.
- I know.
- That's impressive.
They won. I think I'm going to pass out.
(Applauding automatically)
(Creator strategist, Joanne)
(In awe)
Good smell.
(He doesn't miss his chance
to promote it.)
It smells so nice.
(Giving up his hairstyle and going for
a bold decision for pitching)
Your hair will feel soft
even without the conditioner.
I bleached my hair six times.
Those who dyed or bleached their hair
repeatedly like me,
or those with thin hair,
this will help prevent hair loss.
They're very sincere.
That's the spirit.
(Ryota gained confidence.)
(Global reality star and top seller,
Francesca)
(Japanese content entertainment CEO,
Tommy)
(Asking the girl out again
after shampooing)
(She said yes!)
- Okay.
(The nice fragrance resulted
in happy ending.)
Team Japan's First Pitch ends.
That was like Japanese TV ad style.
Yes.
I thought that was really cool.
I thought the whole act
and the whole script...
I get what they were trying to do.
Team Japan's passionate...
and fragrant...
(Rattling)
(His acting is not over yet.)
(No. 1 tech sales in Indonesia, Ibnu)
(Laughing)
(Approved)
(Perfect wrap-up)
Oh, my gosh.
The product is the eye cream.
(Team Thailand's product is
the eye cream.)
(Starting pitching with a skit
just like Team Japan)
They're talking about dark circles.
I have thick dark circles. What do I do?
Maybe you're not getting enough sleep?
(A customer who's worried
about her eyes visits.)
She has thick dark circles.
So you're worried about the wrinkles
around your eyes and dark circles?
(Team Thailand induces empathy
through a skit.)
Here's everybody talking at the same time.
Use this for deep wrinkles
around your eyes...
and the dark area under your eyes.
Team Thailand isn't demonstrating
the product.
They haven't?
Can you see the difference right away
when you apply it?
- Yes, so...
- I see.
If they'd shown,
it'd be evident in the camera.
If you buy it now,
it's buy 1 get 1 free with the promotion.
Not only that, a special sales
and free shipping to your house.
This promotion is only available
during this live show.
(Team Thailand pitched
without demonstration)
Thank you.
(Round 1 pre-mission,
the First Pitch ends.)
The First Pitch.
Now it's time to face the result.
- A seller would recognize a seller best.
- Right.
Please rank each other...
with your objective discernment.
(Voting on the First Pitch begins.)
Let's share who we think is the best.
I think it's either...
They're two opposites.
- If all of them...
- Okay.
were selling to your audience,
which one your audience would buy?
Because you know your audience best.
The most capable team.
They were clearly good.
They were just so-so.
Do we want to give them the points though?
- Because I think they're going to win.
- Yes.
Yes.
We got to put our competitors in check.
I'm submitting it.
Go ahead. We're being really honest.
What do you think of this for the ranking?
(Since it's the first ranking
in X The League...)
- I'm okay with that.
- Then I'll submit this. Thank you.
(Voting ends.)
I'll announce the result
for the First Pitch.
Here is the eighth.
Oh, no. The eighth.
The eighth. We can...
(The rank everyone wants to avoid)
(400,000 in sales in 6 minutes)
I just hope we're not the last.
I don't want to be in the bottom
of the rank.
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman,
Thanh Tuyen)
(A creator with 10 million fans,
Jianhao Tan)
(Exhaling)
Eighth place goes to...
(8th, Vietnam)
Team Vietnam placed eighth.
(Vietnamese media group vice chairwoman,
Thanh Tuyen)
(Vietnam's popular actor
and food CEO, Viet Anh)
(A famous Vietnamese former idol
seller, Hai Dang Doo)
(Team Vietnam violated the rule,
and the owner pitched alone.)
It started to drift too far off
from the product...
to the point where I was like,
"What is she selling?"
I didn't even know what she was selling
at that moment.
(6 countries gave them the lowest points.)
(Team Vietnam recorded the lowest.)
Next is seventh.
- It's Team Thailand.
(7th, Thailand)
Sixth goes to...
(6th, Indonesia)
It's Team Indonesia.
(Bummer)
The fifth country.
It's Team China.
(5th, China)
(0-percent return rate based on trust,
Cui Shishi)
(China in 5th, Indonesia in 6th,
Thailand 7th)
Please show the fourth place...
in the First Pitch mission.
(Global reality star and top seller,
Francesca)
(4th place is close to the upper rank.)
Please.
(Director of an e-commerce company with
cumulative sales of 100 million dollars)
I want the benefit so badly.
- Oh, no.
- No.
(4th, Korea)
What's going on?
(The flags change again.)
- A tie?
- Oh, a tie?
Korea and Japan tied for third.
(Korea and Japan in 3rd)
Congratulations.
(Team Korea divided the roles clearly.)
(It looks like
a TV home shopping channel.)
(They have a firm structure.)
(It's very systematic.)
(Demonstrating the shampoo
by giving up his style)
(Team Japan appealed
with an intuitive skit.)
(That was like Japanese TV ad style.)
(I do like their idea of
trying to win a girl.)
(Both teams were well received
by many countries.)
(J-beauty gyaru icon, Kii chan)
Now we only have the high ranks left.
Okay.
We're either 1st or 2nd.
We're number one.
I think it's us.
The country that's voted number one
by sellers...
will receive the ultimate benefit...
of stealing five percent of
the selected country's total revenue.
(TikTok Shop millionaire)
My heart was like, "Oh, my."
I was excited.
(Malaysian K-beauty sales queen)
We'll get the five percent.
X The League pre-exploration match,
the First Pitch.
Who succeeded...
in taking the initiative...
and stealing the five percent
of total revenue?
We'll reveal it now.
(Not only they explained
the product and the brand,)
(but they also came up
with an imaginary special sales.)
(Team SGMY presented
perfect live commerce.)
(They figured out the characteristic
of the product.)
(Team US proved its performance
before their eyes.)
(Global reality star and top seller)
Five percent of sales steal is unreal.
And I really hope we win...
because that'd be an amazing advantage
for our team.
So I'd say we're just here for the fight,
to have fun,
and experience everything.
But we also want to win.
The winner is...
(Who will win the ultimate benefit
of 5-percent steal ticket by placing 1st?)
Team US. Congratulations.
(1st place, the US)
(Korea's top brand planner, Noh Hee Young)
(Congratulations.)
(K-influencer with 2.8-million-dollar
monthly sales, Xiaoshu Ouni)
- Good job.
- That worked out.
(Hugging happily)
(2nd, Singapore and Malaysia)
(Bummer)
It's bad to be second.
I know. It's bad to be second.
I wouldn't say I was sad.
But it's like, "So annoying."
The first thing that I thought was...
I hope they don't steal our five percent.
(Please.)
We were really happy.
To start the competition with a win is...
such a huge energy boost
and morale boost for the whole team.
Congratulations on taking first place...
in the First Pitch.
After the Round One result announcement,
you may directly select one country
of your choice...
and take five percent of its revenue.
(Team US won the 5-percent steal ticket.)
- Okay.
- Yes.
I know we were thinking...
Yes. We got to think
of who's going to sell...
a lot of products quantity-wise.
I'd say either Korea or China.
I think China.
Actually,
even if Indonesia didn't do very well...
in the First Pitch,
I think with their follower count,
they're going to be super...
We're going to have to really think
about who we pick.
This could be a big increase for us.
So that's exciting. That's huge.
I'm glad we won the first challenge.
- Good job. Good job, team.
- Yes.
It's teamwork.
(What kind of change
will the benefit bring?)
(Now, it's time for real selling.)
(The first match to take the initiative)
Everyone should have denim like this.
(The sellers bring out their own weapons.)
(Round 1 selling period: 20 days)
(The sales battle for their countries)
(And the biggest variable)
I like to see big numbers.
(Team US gathered after Round 1.)
We do get to take
a little bit of something...
from someone. So I think we know who.
(What kind of impact
will the benefit bring?)
Seriously?
(Someone will lose 5 percent
of their revenue.)
Please.
They wouldn't use it on us.
I don't think they'd use it on us.
You know a different country like...
We were thinking about them at first.
- Yes.
- True.
(Team US' benefit makes everyone nervous.)
(And their choice shocks everyone.)
Obviously, there is one
that we want to look at, but...
let's use it effectively.
(The sales battle begins.
What's going to be the result?)
(Round 1 mission, hierarchy reset)
(The sales show who you are.)
(A brutal battle where they're evaluated
solely by number)
(A massive scale that draws attention)
(Famous brands
that will make your jaw drop)
(We can sell this out.)
(This is trending.)
(Give me all the clothes.)
(An intense number battle for victory)
(They start selling in their countries.)
(The beginning of a new hierarchy reset
between 40 sellers)
(Reach the highest sales...)
(by all means.)
(About 540 dollars)
(The interim record is lower
than expected.)
(How is it going to end?)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)